<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bruco on Bruco 🐛</title><link>https://ferama.github.io/bruco/</link><description>Recent content in Bruco on Bruco 🐛</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ferama.github.io/bruco/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Http</title><link>https://ferama.github.io/bruco/sources/http/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ferama.github.io/bruco/sources/http/</guid><description>The http source is activated using the http kind
yaml path description ignoreProcessorResponse If true doen&amp;rsquo;t return the prcessed value to the http caller port the port the http server listens too (do not change this if you are using bruco with k8s) Example:
source: kind: http ignoreProcessorResponse: false # port: 8090</description></item><item><title>Kafka</title><link>https://ferama.github.io/bruco/sinks/kafka/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ferama.github.io/bruco/sinks/kafka/</guid><description>The kafka sink is activated using the kafka kind
Example:
# OPTIONAL: you can have a source and a processor without a sink sink: kind: kafka brokers: - localhost:9092 topic: test-out # OPTIONAL: target partition partition: 42 # OPTIONAL: default hash if partition is not defined. values: manual, hash, random partitioner: hash</description></item><item><title>Kafka</title><link>https://ferama.github.io/bruco/sources/kafka/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ferama.github.io/bruco/sources/kafka/</guid><description>Bruco uses Sarama (https://github.com/Shopify/sarama) as kafka library.
The kafka source is activated using the kafka kind
yaml path description brokers a list of kafka brokers to connect to topics a list of topics to subscribe too offset the initial offset where the kafka consumer will start to consume consumerGroup the kafka consumer group balanceStrategy the kafka consumer balance startegy fireAndForget if true, the first available worker will process a message, regardless of partition message order rebalanceTimeout kafka rebalanceTimeout channelBufferSize the size of consumer buffer fetchDefaultBytes the size in bytes to fetch from the topic each time Example:</description></item><item><title>NATS</title><link>https://ferama.github.io/bruco/sinks/nats/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ferama.github.io/bruco/sinks/nats/</guid><description>The nats sink is activated using the nats kind
Example:
# OPTIONAL: you can have a source and a processor without a sink sink: kind: nats serverUrl: localhost:4222 subject: out.sub</description></item><item><title>NATS</title><link>https://ferama.github.io/bruco/sources/nats/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ferama.github.io/bruco/sources/nats/</guid><description>The NATS source is activated using the nats kind
Example:
source: kind: nats serverUrl: localhost:4222 queueGroup: test subject: in.sub</description></item><item><title>Getting started on k8s</title><link>https://ferama.github.io/bruco/basic/getting-started/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ferama.github.io/bruco/basic/getting-started/</guid><description>This guide will introduce you to the bruco concept e will help to get the stuff up and running quickly.
This tutorial make some assumptions:
You have a kubernetes environment up and running You have correctly configured the kubectl cli tool to interact with the env above Bruco is heavily integrated with Kubernetes. To get start to experiment with bruco function deployment you need to setup some stuff on kubernetes first.</description></item></channel></rss>